question_data = [
        {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Snakes and Ladders was originally created in India?", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                           "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.",
                                           "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In &quot;Mario Kart 64&quot;, Waluigi is a playable character.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                          "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
                                          "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The United States Department of Homeland Security was formed in response to the September 11th attacks.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Tetris is the #1 best-selling video game of all-time.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Denmark has a monarch.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The card game &quot;Munchkin&quot; won the 2001 Origins Award for Best Traditional Card Game.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In Team Fortress 2, being disguised as a scout or medic results in a speed boost.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The NVidia GTX 1080 gets its name because it can only render at a 1920x1080 screen resolution.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Valve&#039;s &quot;Portal&quot; and &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchises exist within the same in-game universe.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Donald Trump won the popular vote in the 2016 United States presidential election.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Hungary is the only country in the world beginning with H.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In Chobits, Hideki found Chii in his apartment.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                          "question": "A scalene triangle has two sides of equal length.",
                                          "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In the video game &quot;Splatoon&quot;, the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]

